{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes P, G, S, N and directed edges P->N, G->S, P->S, P->G.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all parents of node N.", "answer": "{'P'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many children does node P have?", "answer": "3"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node G one of ancestors of node P?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of descendants of node P?\nA. S\nB. T\nC. E\nD. W", "answer": "A"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node G have any descendants?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "11378664", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes H, I, A, T and directed edges H->I, H->A, H->T, I->T, I->A, A->T.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all descendants of node I.", "answer": "{'T', 'A'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many ancestors does node A have?", "answer": "2"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node T one of ancestors of node H?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of descendants of node I?\nA. N\nB. T\nC. L\nD. H", "answer": "B"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node I have any descendants?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "23435083", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, X, L, U, N and directed edges M->X, U->N, M->U, L->U, M->L, M->N, L->N.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all descendants of node L.", "answer": "{'U', 'N'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many children does node X have?", "answer": "0"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node X one of children of node U?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of descendants of node U?\nA. N\nB. X\nC. L\nD. M", "answer": "A"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node M have any descendants?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "09478135", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes M, Z, A, X, R and directed edges M->X, X->R, Z->A, M->Z, M->R, Z->X, Z->R.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all children of node X.", "answer": "{'R'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many parents does node Z have?", "answer": "1"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node Z one of ancestors of node X?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of ancestors of node R?\nA. K\nB. H\nC. A\nD. Z", "answer": "D"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node A have any children?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "12573711", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes B, N, V, R, D, C and directed edges D->C, V->R, B->D, N->C, V->D, B->V, R->D, R->C, N->R.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all ancestors of node V.", "answer": "{'B'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many descendants does node C have?", "answer": "0"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node N one of parents of node R?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of descendants of node D?\nA. R\nB. B\nC. V\nD. C", "answer": "D"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node D have any children?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "57969567", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes Q, H, G, Y, L, T and directed edges H->T, Q->H, G->L, H->L, Q->G, G->Y, Q->Y, Y->T, H->Y, Y->L.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all children of node H.", "answer": "{'T', 'L', 'Y'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many parents does node H have?", "answer": "1"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node H one of descendants of node Y?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of parents of node T?\nA. H\nB. Q\nC. L\nD. G", "answer": "A"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node T have any ancestors?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "62640566", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes I, S, T, L, W, D, M and directed edges I->S, W->M, T->W, W->D, I->L, S->L, L->W, L->D, T->L.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all children of node L.", "answer": "{'D', 'W'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many ancestors does node W have?", "answer": "4"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node T one of children of node I?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of parents of node L?\nA. D\nB. W\nC. M\nD. T", "answer": "D"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node D have any descendants?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "07805756", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes V, N, J, Q, Z, F, T and directed edges N->Z, N->Q, Z->T, Q->T, N->F, Q->F, V->Z, J->Q.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all ancestors of node T.", "answer": "{'Z', 'J', 'V', 'Q', 'N'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many ancestors does node Q have?", "answer": "2"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node T one of descendants of node V?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of descendants of node Q?\nA. J\nB. V\nC. N\nD. F", "answer": "D"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node F have any parents?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "50998853", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes G, L, J, U, V, Q, A, W and directed edges U->V, L->U, J->Q, U->Q, L->V, J->W, L->W, G->W, Q->A.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all children of node J.", "answer": "{'Q', 'W'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many descendants does node U have?", "answer": "3"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node W one of ancestors of node V?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of ancestors of node A?\nA. W\nB. G\nC. V\nD. L", "answer": "D"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node L have any ancestors?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "52465487", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes U, R, P, E, W, M, I, K and directed edges P->E, U->M, P->I, E->K, U->W, U->P, U->I, E->W, R->M.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all children of node E.", "answer": "{'K', 'W'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many ancestors does node K have?", "answer": "3"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node R one of descendants of node W?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of children of node R?\nA. M\nB. I\nC. K\nD. W", "answer": "A"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node P have any ancestors?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "30841726", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes X, Y, T, P, H, M, I, W, V and directed edges T->V, X->M, T->P, X->V, H->M, T->W, H->I, P->I, Y->M, Y->T.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all children of node Y.", "answer": "{'T', 'M'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many descendants does node M have?", "answer": "0"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node T one of parents of node M?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of ancestors of node I?\nA. V\nB. X\nC. P\nD. W", "answer": "C"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node I have any descendants?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "88813945", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given a DAG (directed acyclic graph) with nodes E, G, C, L, M, Z, R, W, U and directed edges M->Z, E->W, Z->U, Z->R, C->L, G->L, G->Z, M->U, C->W, L->W.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all children of node M.", "answer": "{'Z', 'U'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many descendants does node Z have?", "answer": "2"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node W one of parents of node Z?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of children of node M?\nA. C\nB. W\nC. U\nD. L", "answer": "C"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node G have any parents?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "32652475", "graph_type": "DAG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes T, R, W, Z, directed edges R->Z, W->Z, T->W and bi-directed edges T<->W.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all descendants of node R.", "answer": "{'Z'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many ancestors does node W have?", "answer": "1"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node R one of descendants of node T?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of children of node R?\nA. W\nB. T\nC. Z\nD. B", "answer": "C"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node T have any ancestors?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "55639177", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes Q, Y, B, X, directed edges Y->B, Q->B, Q->X, Y->X, Q->Y and bi-directed edges Q<->B, Y<->X.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all parents of node Y.", "answer": "{'Q'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many parents does node X have?", "answer": "2"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node B one of parents of node X?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of descendants of node Q?\nA. X\nB. G\nC. P\nD. R", "answer": "A"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node Y have any parents?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "39363780", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, Y, L, V, M, directed edges L->V, B->V, Y->V, Y->M, B->Y, B->L, B->M, Y->L, V->M, L->M and bi-directed edges B<->Y, V<->M, Y<->M, L<->V, Y<->V.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all parents of node M.", "answer": "{'L', 'V', 'Y', 'B'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many parents does node V have?", "answer": "3"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node V one of ancestors of node Y?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of descendants of node L?\nA. M\nB. P\nC. Y\nD. B", "answer": "A"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node V have any descendants?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "09810484", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes A, T, D, P, H, directed edges D->P, T->H, P->H, A->P, T->D and bi-directed edges D<->P.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all parents of node P.", "answer": "{'A', 'D'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many parents does node H have?", "answer": "2"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node H one of parents of node P?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of ancestors of node D?\nA. A\nB. T\nC. H\nD. P", "answer": "B"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node D have any children?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "05238884", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes P, Y, F, A, T, K, directed edges Y->K, F->A, T->K, P->A, Y->T, P->T and bi-directed edges Y<->T, P<->A.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all ancestors of node K.", "answer": "{'T', 'Y', 'P'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many children does node K have?", "answer": "0"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node P one of descendants of node Y?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of children of node T?\nA. F\nB. K\nC. A\nD. P", "answer": "B"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node T have any ancestors?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "84323466", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes B, M, I, C, N, G, directed edges M->I, N->G, M->N, B->N, B->C, B->G, I->G, I->N, B->M, B->I and bi-directed edges M<->G, B<->M, I<->N, M<->N, B<->N.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all children of node N.", "answer": "{'G'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many parents does node M have?", "answer": "1"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node B one of descendants of node C?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of children of node I?\nA. B\nB. C\nC. M\nD. G", "answer": "D"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node B have any parents?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "15404880", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes K, Q, S, A, P, I, Y, directed edges K->I, S->P, K->P, P->Y, K->Q, A->Y, S->I, Q->I and bi-directed edges K<->I, Q<->S, P<->Y, K<->Q.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all children of node S.", "answer": "{'I', 'P'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many children does node Y have?", "answer": "0"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node K one of children of node A?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of children of node K?\nA. Y\nB. S\nC. I\nD. A", "answer": "C"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node I have any descendants?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "66807141", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes I, N, O, X, M, S, R, directed edges S->R, X->S, O->R, I->S, O->X, N->O, I->M, I->N, N->S, I->X and bi-directed edges N<->O, O<->M, X<->R.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all descendants of node I.", "answer": "{'S', 'R', 'M', 'O', 'N', 'X'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many ancestors does node I have?", "answer": "0"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node X one of descendants of node I?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of children of node S?\nA. N\nB. O\nC. R\nD. I", "answer": "C"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node S have any children?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "34995436", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes C, I, B, F, E, K, M, N, directed edges B->M, I->B, M->N, C->B, F->K, I->F, I->N, K->M, E->K, E->M and bi-directed edges M<->N, I<->F, B<->K, F<->M, F<->N.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all parents of node N.", "answer": "{'M', 'I'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many parents does node N have?", "answer": "2"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node B one of children of node K?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of parents of node N?\nA. I\nB. F\nC. C\nD. B", "answer": "A"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node B have any ancestors?", "answer": "Yes."}], "uid": "65638086", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes C, G, V, H, I, N, Y, P, directed edges G->V, C->I, V->H, H->N, H->I, Y->P, C->Y and bi-directed edges V<->H, G<->N, C<->H.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all ancestors of node Y.", "answer": "{'C'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many descendants does node Y have?", "answer": "1"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node I one of descendants of node V?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of parents of node N?\nA. C\nB. G\nC. V\nD. H", "answer": "D"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node I have any descendants?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "17042156", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes H, W, D, C, Q, U, V, Y, X, directed edges V->X, Y->X, C->X, D->Q, W->D, H->U, Q->X, U->V and bi-directed edges U<->Y, W<->X, H<->D, H<->Q.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all children of node W.", "answer": "{'D'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many descendants does node V have?", "answer": "1"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node C one of children of node W?", "answer": "No."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of descendants of node W?\nA. U\nB. V\nC. Q\nD. C", "answer": "C"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node W have any parents?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "89441746", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
{"description": "Given an ADMG (acyclic directed mixed graph) with nodes W, A, S, Q, O, L, U, T, X, directed edges A->Q, T->X, O->L, O->X, S->O, S->Q, W->L, S->U and bi-directed edges W<->T, W<->Q, A<->U.", "questions_and_answers": [{"question_type": "FA", "question": "List all ancestors of node X.", "answer": "{'T', 'S', 'O'}"}, {"question_type": "HM", "question": "How many children does node W have?", "answer": "1"}, {"question_type": "YN", "question": "Is node S one of ancestors of node U?", "answer": "Yes."}, {"question_type": "MC", "question": "Which of the following is one of descendants of node T?\nA. O\nB. W\nC. X\nD. U", "answer": "C"}, {"question_type": "EX", "question": "Does node T have any ancestors?", "answer": "No."}], "uid": "97200705", "graph_type": "ADMG"}
